21 Up is a documentary film directed by Michael Apted.
After another 7 year wait, director Michael Apted revisits the
same group of British-born children from Seven Up!
and 7 Plus Seven.
The subjects are interviewed as to the changes that have
occurred in their lives during the last seven years.
Self, played by Lynn Johnson.
Self, played by Tony Walker.
Self, played by Jacqueline Bassett.
Self, played by Charles Furneaux.
Self, played by Bruce Balden.
Self, played by Andrew Brackfield.
Julia is a 1977 American political drama film directed by
Fred Zinnemann and written by Alvin Sargent.
It is based on a chapter from Lillian Hellman's 1973 book Pentimento about the author's relationship with a
lifelong friend, Julia, who fought against the Nazis in the years prior to World War II.
The film stars Jane Fonda as Hellman and Vanessa Redgrave as Julia.
It co-stars Jason Robards, Hal Holbrook, Rosemary Murphy,
Maximilian Schell, and Meryl Streep (in her film debut).
Julia released theatrically on October 2, 1977, by 20th Century Fox.
The film received positive reviews from critics and grossed
$20.7 million against a $7 million budget.
It received a leading 11 nominations at the 50th Academy Awards, including Best Picture, and won three awards: Best
Supporting Actor (for Robards), Best Supporting Actress (for Redgrave) and Best Adapted Screenplay.